When Python has a problem with your code,
当 Python 有代码的问题时
it will tell you which line number it was working on when the problem happened.
它会告诉你问题发生时它正在做什么线号
In the case of this code,
在此代码的情况下
the first problem shows up on line two.
第一个问题出现在第二行
Now by itself, this line of code looks just fine.
现在 这一行代码看起来很不错
We saw lines of code just like this one before and they worked.
我们看到的代码就像这样 然后他们就开始工作了
We were able to set turtles colors to be yellow,
我们可以把海龟的颜色设置为黄色
or green, or whatever we like.
或者绿色 或者我们喜欢的任何东西
What's going on here? Why is this lineup problem now?
这是怎么回事 为什么现在这个阵容问题 ?
Well, normally, Python runs code from top to
通常  Python 运行代码从顶部到
bottom in the same way that you would carry out a series of instructions.
以同样的方式下底你会执行一系列的指令
The computer runs line one first,
电脑第一行
then line two and so on.
那就行了
But, this means that the instructions have to be in the right order.
但是 这意味着指令必须符合正确的顺序
If they're in the wrong order,
如果他们的顺序不对
the computer will probably get lost,
电脑可能会丢失
and that's what's happening here.
这就是这里发生的事情
Take another look at these first three lines of this program.
再看看这个节目的前三行
The program tries to get a turtle named Melinda to do something on line two.
节目试图让一只名叫梅林达的乌龟在两线上做点什么
But, we don't actually say to create a turtle named Melinda until line three.
但是 我们并不是说要创建一只名叫梅林达的乌龟 直到第三行
The program can't tell Melinda what to do if there isn't a turtle with that name yet.
节目不能告诉梅林达 如果还没有一个有这个名字的海龟 怎么办 ?
The error message, name error,
错误消息 名称错误
will always mean that the code is referring to
通常是指代码是指
a name that doesn't actually refer to any object yet.
一个还没有提到任何对象的名字
The rest of the error message tells you exactly what name is
剩下的错误信息告诉你
having the problem and what line in the code it occurs on.
问题以及代码发生在什么代码中
So all we need to do to fix this error is to put these two lines into the correct order.
所以我们要解决的问题就是把这两条线输入正确的顺序
Once we do that, the code can start running,
一旦我们做到了密码就能开始运行
at least until the next error happens.
至少在下一个错误发生之前
Try it then see if you can fix that one too.
试一下 看看你也能修好那个